[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
THE SHINY BLACK NOSE BEFORE ME
[Legoshi growling]
- [Seven trembling, whimpering]
- [heart beating]
[growling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sniffing, growling]
[Seven] He's going to kill me. I...
I have to call someone.
[breathing heavily]
- [straining]
- [Legoshi growling]
[Legoshi] Just calm down.
Control yourself.
Eat me, Legoshi!
[Legoshi] Living herbivore meat.
Oh, it's too good to resist.
[screaming]
[straining]
- [growls]
- [yelps]
[Legoshi straining, breathing heavily]
[Seven whimpering softly]
[suspenseful music intensifies]
[Legoshi straining] Ms. Seven.
[Legoshi breathing heavily]
[music stops]
[exhales]
It is Ms. Seven, right?
- [panting]
- Yes.
My room...
The electricity is out.
What am I supposed to do?
[Seven stuttering]
You call the electric company, and...
and tell them your address.
[Legoshi] The electric company?
Yeah. Just tell them where you live,
and they can turn it on remotely.
[grunts softly]
Hmm?
[amusing music playing]
Do you have a cellphone?
You should be able
to find the number on Zoozle.
I, uh...
I canceled my contract
when I dropped out of school.
What?
[reading] "World History,"
"Ocean Language," "GED Test Prep"?
Are you still a teenager?
Uh... I'm 17.
I'm working at an udon restaurant now.
[Seven] Hmm.
Your shoes are a little old-fashioned
for a teenager.
Well, when you're a large carnivore,
you don't have a whole lot of options.
Ah. Yeah, I suppose you're right.
- Huh?
- You know, I actually work for that brand.
Wha-- Is that right?
Well, keep up the good work.
[sighs]
Good. Small talk like this
helps keep my appetite at bay.
So, uh...
Anyway, my name is Legoshi.
Look, I'm sorry
I didn't introduce myself sooner.
- Those scars...
- [Legoshi] Not like I wasn't in the mood.
- [yelps]
- [Seven gasps]
[yelping, breathing heavily]
- Please don't touch me!
- What?
Please.
[sighs]
Well, I'll look up that number.
I can do that for you.
[keypad clicking]
Can I ask...
I don't know if this is going to be
a weird thing for you to answer or not,
but why are you staying here with me
instead of running?
[Seven] Hmm?
Hmm.
Well, to be honest, I'm not used to
carnivores calling me by my name.
And I thought that was nice.
[indistinct chatter]
I heard some senior drank
one of those things. He lost it!
And he wound up biting
his girlfriend's finger off.
- No way that's real!
- It was on the news and everything, dude.
It's true!
But, hey, you can try it
if you don't believe me.
You know what? I don't think
I want to push my luck.
Man, don't be a baby!
- Try it.
- [hesitates] Uh...
[grunts]
Huh? This sucker's empty!
- [laughing]
- [can clanging]
What is with you, dude?
Can't stand you sometimes!
[both] Huh?
[both] Uh...
Ah, if it isn't the little lord.
Forgive our rudeness,
it shan't happen again!
- [hyena laughs]
- I'll throw it out for you.
- Nah, it's cool. I got it.
- [hyena laughing]
We're just yanking your horns.
We'd get kicked out of school
if we actually tried to mess with ya.
[hyena] Plus, piss off
The Horns Conglomerate,
and you can say goodbye
to a decent job anywhere.
[lion] Anyway, I'll take that.
I said, give it here!
Meat intoxication?
[gasps]
Those withdrawal symptoms are nasty.
- Is this what's causing them?
- I said, give it back!
[lion grunts, strains]
[Louis] Truly an underhanded way
to take a carnivore off their feet.
[strains, yelps]
[grunts]
[Louis] A little trick I picked up
from the Shishi-Gumi.
Listen up. A lion's strength
is a weapon that must be honed.
Don't misuse it, lest it chip.
[growling]
Oh, wow.
It's kind of elegant.
Surely, it doesn't hurt anymore, right?
[Louis] It hasn't been
nearly as bad as I thought.
I don't exactly understand
why you're showing me.
You're the only one who knows I was ever
in the Black Market in the first place.
I don't know, maybe that's all it is.
It makes sense
you just want someone to know.
Well--
If you're worried about it,
though, that's okay.
[hesitates] I don't care.
Deer shed their antlers
once a year, every year,
so you'll understand
we're not the type to make a fuss
over losing parts of our bodies.
Besides--
[romantic guitar music playing]
[Juno gasps softly] Uh...
[hesitates] I... I don't know why I...
Oh, my gosh, I'm so sorry!
Why did-- I shouldn't--
- Can we just pretend that didn't happen--
- Don't freak out. It never happened.
It-- Hang on a second!
You can't forget it that easily!
- I just gave you my first kiss ever!
- Hey!
- Would you calm down?
- Calm down?
You kissed me because you wanted
to show mercy to a poor injured herbivore.
This conversation is over.
Why would you say something like that?
That really hurts my feelings.
[sighs] I, uh, hope all is well
with the club activities.
There is no good to be found
in falling in love
with someone from another species.
So why am I...
- [sighs]
- [indistinct chatter]
[Louis] I thought I had severed
my ties with the carnivores.
Why can't I seem to shake them off?
[scoffs]
[indistinct chatter]
- [thudding]
- [footstep thuds]
- [can cracks open]
- [drink fizzes]
[sighs]
[exhales]
[inhales deeply]
[laughs]
[gulping]
[ominous music playing]
[sighs contentedly, laughs]
Huh?
[gasps]
[gagging]
[straining]
[breathing heavily]
[growling]
[train rattling]
[footsteps approaching]
How long you want to bet
this guy's going to keep us waiting?
Right? And after all that talk
about rebranding us too!
- [clanking]
- [both] Hmm?
[Free] Huh? What is that?
- Hmm.
- Huh?
[both] Hmm.
- [low growling]
- [Free] Hmm?
[suspenseful music playing]
Jimma?
[growling]
Stop! What's your deal?
[all grunting]
[Agata] Calm down! What's wrong with you?
- That's it. [grunts]
- [Jimma groans]
[Jimma breathing heavily]
[Free] You dumbass.
What the hell were you thinking?
[Dolph] Who put you up to this?
[groans] I don't know...
Yeah, right.
[heavy footsteps approaching]
[all] Hmm?
Is that him?
[Melon] You should know better
than to get high on your own supply.
What? You make it sound like
we're drug dealers or something.
[Dolph] This isn't
a regular energy drink I'm guessing.
[Melon] Kines contains
the flesh and bones of herbivores.
Though admittedly only a small amount,
it's just enough to satisfy
a meat craving.
Give you a little extra boost of vitality.
[footsteps thudding]
But if you drink too much,
one day, it won't be enough.
That's when they come to the Black Market,
seeking real meat.
So, thanks to the Shishi-Gumi,
Black Market business is booming.
[Melon] Unfortunately,
when someone drinks it,
who's experienced the real thing...
Well...
[Free] Yeah, I get it.
[Jimma groans softly] Huh?
[all] Huh?
[Melon] Deliver it to this address.
"Gardona and Algama... Center Street"?
You want us to go out
and sell this mainstream?
[Melon] Oh, no, no, no. Just deliver it.
Your hideous faces
couldn't sell water to a fish.
- We haven't agreed to do it yet!
- [both] Huh?
You found a single piece of ivory.
It'll take more than that
for you to be the boss.
[Melon] Oh. I guess you have a point.
[loud clamp]
- [heavy thud]
- [gasps]
[all gasping]
[Melon] How's this?
[lions breath trembling]
[car horns honking]
[leopard] Look who it is!
Hey, Little Lamb!
Inspecting the sales floor on a day off?
Yeah, ever the diligent employee, I see.
Well, turns out, so are we. [laughs]
[Seven] Ugh! It's just my luck
to run into these two.
What a waste of a lovely day.
The herbivore department's
been on fire lately,
so I'd say you've earned a little break.
[chuckles] Yes, maybe you're right.
But no matter, I can deal with them
easily enough.
A fake smile always seems to do the trick.
We carnivores have a harder time selling.
But all you've got to do
- is flash those pearly whites of yours.
- [Legoshi] Hey, uh...
- [Seven] Hmm?
- [leopard] Huh?
Sorry, these are a little small.
[both trembling]
- This guy a friend of yours?
- [Seven] Huh?
[Legoshi] I'm her neighbor.
[laughs] You had me going there!
Thought he was the boyfriend.
- No, just the neighbor.
- [Seven chuckling] Oh, goodness no.
And this lady's name is Ms. Seven,
by the way.
- [gasps]
- Not "Little Lamb."
Unless that's, like,
a work nickname? I don't know.
Yeah, it's... it's a nickname.
Just a little joke
between coworkers, right?
CLEARANCE SALE. 5300 YEN
[leopard] Uh, sure, yeah.
We didn't mean anything by it.
- [hesitates] Uh...
- [sighs]
Uh, now that I think about it,
it's way too mean.
Who even started that? You?
Uh, no, no! It was the boss.
Uh, anyway, sorry to bother you.
We should get going.
[sighs] We'll see you around, Ms. Seven.
[Seven] What just happened?
All these years, I've had to put up
with these bullies, and now they just...
[Legoshi] Are you okay?
It looked like
they had you cornered there.
[Seven] Just because he's...
So, I suppose you think you've saved me?
[stutters]
- [tires screech]
- [Legoshi] Hey, wait! I'm sorry!
Are you upset because those guys thought
I was your boyfriend?
'Cause I tried to tell them.
[Seven sighs] Unbelievable!
He really is just a little kid!
- He's a child!
- [Legoshi chatters indistinctly]
Tell me, why is it that someone like you
has more authority
- in the social hierarchy than I do?
- Huh?
You're not even a functioning adult yet,
and you still managed
to shut them up in seconds
without so much as a courtesy smile!
And how? By being a great, big carnivore?
You better watch it, wolf!
- I'll report you!
- [Legoshi chuckles nervously]
[Seven] Oh, no, that's okay.
[chuckles nervously, sighs]
[amusing music playing]
[Legoshi] I didn't even consider that.
She's been treated in ways
I've never had to experience before.
And maybe never will.
[pops]
[gulping]
[sighs contentedly]
- [Legoshi] Ms. Seven?
- Huh?
What, so you're following me now?
Leave me alone so I can drink in peace!
[Legoshi] I'm sorry. I acted
without thinking, and that was rude.
[sighs] Just let it go.
You'll learn as you get older.
It feels miserable when you want
an apology from someone
and they actually give it to you.
Then, what do I say?
- You don't have to say anything at all.
- Huh?
I'm not upset with you.
You did nothing wrong.
Should I not respond to that either, or...
[chuckles] You need to relax a little.
[cans thud softly]
- [boat engine whirring]
- [horn blares]
[black panther] Mmm.
If you pocketed a stack of cash or two,
what would you eat with it?
Don't make jokes like that.
You'll get yourself killed.
- [squeaking, chattering]
- Huh?
[mysterious music playing]
- [gasps softly]
- Hmm? Is that Gohin?
It's not Gohin.
It's The 500 Cornered Rats!
[yells in pain]
- [whimpering]
- Jeez, are you all right?
[gasps] Hey, hold it!
You wait right there!
Uh... They're splitting up! What do we do?
That's Shishi-Gumi money!
You think I don't know that?
[rats chittering]
[rats exclaim, squeak excitedly]
- [Corne] Toodle-oo!
- [pants, grunts in frustration]
- [rats squeaking]
- [grunting, indistinct shouting]
[Corne] We are The 500 Cornered Rats.
We steal from the bad people.
By mobilizing our huge base,
we can influence not only
the Black Market economy, but everybody.
Got to admit, the job's got its perks.
[chittering]
[grunting]
[indistinct shouting]
- [grunts]
- [rats groan]
It was you filthy rats that stole
the mayor's gold watch, wasn't it?
- Spill it!
- [grunting]
[officer] We're the police,
and even we couldn't care less
if a bunch of punk rats just up and died.
No, no, all lives are equal.
- [both gasp]
- Mr. Yahya!
Larger species like you
that tower over a lot of the other ones,
species so small,
they can't even trigger automatic doors,
and even yours truly...
We're all the same...
Every species equally insignificant.
And saving those poor insignificant lives
is my charge for better or worse.
Those jerks! [groans]
Just because we're rats. [groans]
Sounds like a case
of making your own bed, I'm afraid.
So, any new ideas?
Well, it's not Doku-Gumi, Inari-Gumi,
or Madara-Gumi.
No other leads so far.
- And what about Shishi-Gumi?
- Can't be them.
Without a stable leader,
Shishi-Gumi wouldn't be able
to handle something like Kines.
And, unfortunately, it's available
way more than we anticipated.
UDON BEBEBE
[Yahya] It's circulating
in mainstream society now?
[Legoshi] Anyway, good night.
[Corne] Damn straight.
And, apparently, young carnivores
have been getting their hands
on this stuff pretty quickly.
[Yahya] According
to the forensic analysis,
it appears to contain
several narcotic-like components.
Those most at risk are carnivores
with previous experience
of meat consumption.
Apparently, even a single dose
can induce side effects,
which include a strong craving for meat
and increased aggressiveness.
[Legoshi] It's the first money
I've ever earned on my own.
I should pay the rent
and my electric bills first,
but then, flowers for Haru.
I think I'm going to do well
for myself here.
So, I want to make sure
I do right by Haru too.
No more secrets.
Hey, young man!
Excuse me, hello. Good evening, sir.
Hi, good evening.
[black panther chuckles wickedly] Mmm.
How would you like to try
a special energy drink,
just for carnivores?
You seem very tired this evening.
And it seems like the people out there
pushing this stuff
have no clue about those side effects.
If we're not very careful,
before too long, we could have carnivores
killing each other in the streets.
Uh, I'm okay. I have more stamina
than you would think.
Nah, come on, come on.
Just trust me, you'll love it.
You can try one, it won't hurt.
[drink fizzes]
Hmm?
Mmm...
[soft growling]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
-♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪